Narrator: 1
Rooms
Speaker: a bathroom
Narrator: 5
Speaker: a bedroom
Narrator: 7
Speaker: a dining room
Narrator: 10
Speaker: a garage
Narrator: 6
Speaker: a garden
Narrator: 8
Speaker: a hall
Narrator: 9
Speaker: a kitchen
Narrator: 3
Speaker: a living room
Narrator: 2
Speaker: a study
Narrator: 1
Speaker: a toilet
Narrator: 2
Parts of a room
Speaker: a balcony
Narrator: 11
Speaker: a ceiling
Narrator: 15
Speaker: a floor
Narrator: 14
Speaker: stairs
Narrator: 13
Speaker: a wall
Narrator: 3
Things in a room
Narrator: 22
Speaker: an armchair
Narrator: 23
Speaker: a bath
Narrator: 26
Speaker: a bed
Narrator: 27
Speaker: a carpet
Narrator: 34
Speaker: a cooker
Narrator: 29
Speaker: a cupboard
Narrator: 32
Speaker: a dishwasher
Narrator: 21
Speaker: a fireplace
Narrator: 28
Speaker: a fridge
Narrator: 18
Speaker: a light
Narrator: 30
Speaker: a microwave
Narrator: 16
Speaker: a mirror
Narrator: 19
Speaker: a plant
Narrator: 17
Speaker: a shelf
Narrator: 24
Speaker: a shower
Narrator: 33
Speaker: a sink
Narrator: 20
Speaker: a sofa
Narrator: 25
Speaker: a wardrobe
Narrator: 31
Speaker: a washing machine